Ours was a love story like no other.
It's like a film written by Ricky Lee.
But in our version,
she's no damsel in distress.
She needed no saving.
As a matter of fact,
I was the one who needed to be saved.
Mister! Help! Help!
There's a giant crocodile!
Sorry, Mister. I'm going to an audition.
Sorry.
This is not the first time I've seen her.
I've known her for a long time.
She was my classmate in college.
If there's one thing permanent in our lives,
it's change.
Everything changes.
You can change everything.
That's the nature of reality,
according to our Greek philosopher Heraclitus.
Professor, I think...
I think my father would disagree.
Why is that, Miss Trinidad?
Because for him,
a lot of things are permanent in our lives.
Like death, taxes...
including his fear of my mom.
She was popular in college.
I'm not sure if she knew me.
All I know is...
my world becomes brighter whenever I see her.
Why I didn't introduce myself to her...
Why I did not approach her...
Why I did not befriend her...
Why I didn't try to court her.
Let's just say
I'm waiting for the right time and opportunity
to approach her.
Unfortunately, I ran out of time.
That was the last time I saw her.
The next semester,
we heard she dropped out of the university.
And no one could tell
what had happened to her.
I was like Ely Buendia
the next time I saw her.
The same way he saw
his kind of ugly friend in a magazine.
She was wearing yellow,
and her hair was green.
But unlike in the song, I didn't judge her.
Instead, I felt pride.
Because the world deserves to know
the most beautiful woman I've ever seen.
The woman
who can make my heart beat fast and slow.
Is this fate?
Or is it divine providence?
Imagine, after a long time, here she is.
We are on the same trip.
This is supposed
to be an escape from the city.
But here I am,
facing the feelings
I've long been trying to escape.
Has the Universe given me the right time
to introduce myself to her?
Is this the beginning of
my happily ever after?
Those who are getting off, be ready.
We'll be at the bus stop in a few minutes.
This is the stop!
Time to wake up!
Wake up!
This is your stop.
We've reached Huseña!
Hurry up!
Is it true that like a rosary,
love is full of mystery?
Love isn't so mysterious, son.
People just make it complicated sometimes.
For me, love is very simple.
Love is an act of bravery.
You need to be brave
when opening your heart to others.
Love is an act of bravery.
Has everyone gotten off?
Hey...
Sorry, I wasn't looking.
I'm sorry.
[Restroom]
Ouch! Ouch!
- What? Here! Get this! Who are you?
- That hurts!
You've been following me!
You think I wouldn't notice?
- Pervert! Pervert!
- What do you mean?
I'm not a pervert!
- You're a robber!
- Come on, Joyce!
I'm Liam!
That hurts!
How do you know my name?
Are you a stalker?
- No...
- A rapist and a stalker.
- Robber!
- I'm not...
A rapist who's also a stalker!
Joyce! Joyce, calm down!
I'm Liam. We were classmates in Agustin!
It stings.
You were my classmate in Agustin?
Yes, we were classmates in Philosophy 101
under Professor Malvarosa.
It hurts.
We were classmates?
- Yes.
- Are you sure?
Yes, I am. We were classmates.
What did you say your name was?
Liam.
Liam?
William Herrera.
Go on.
- Do I just pour it?
- Yes.
Sorry!
I'm sorry. I'm really sorry.
Sorry. Well, it was your fault.
Why were you following me?
Honestly, you can't blame me.
You know how dangerous this world is
for women.
Innocent women get killed.
It's so unsafe nowadays. I'm sorry.
Sorry.
That's okay, Joyce.
You're right.
I should apologize because I startled you.
But I didn't mean it.
It's okay.
So...
What lesson did you learn today?
What lesson did I learn today?
Pepper spray hurts.
Also...
That pepper spray can be used
any time of the day.
Also...
I shouldn't just follow anyone
without being careful.
You can be mistaken for a crook.
Look at what I've done to you.
Sorry.
Wait, so why were you following me?
Do you need...
Did I owe you money I haven't paid yet?
Sorry! Sorry!
- This is embarrassing!
- Joyce, Joyce...
Sorry!
You don't owe me anything.
Nothing.
I followed you, because...
I wanted to...
At that moment, I wanted to confess to her.
The truth is, I followed her
because I wanted to introduce myself to her.
I was hoping I could ask her out
to have coffee with me.
Or maybe see a movie.
But just like before,
I didn't have enough courage.
- Cheers to our professor!
- Cheers!
Cheers!
Instead, I told her
that Malvarosa, our philosophy professor,
will be having a send-off party.
She and her husband would be migrating
to France,
and she is inviting all of her students.
And that's the reason why I followed her.
To tell her
that I thought she might want to attend.
She was one of our professor's favorites,
after all.
That's what I was saying...
Let's take a picture!
Everyone. One, two, smile.
Maybe he's looking
for a girl he can dance with.
- We have to find a girl.
- Oh, you!
Come on, let's eat.
- Oh, yeah.
- Let's go.
- Ma'am.
- Go get some food.
Are you waiting for...
a shooting star so you can make a wish?
Am I not too old to make wishes upon a star?
You're right.
I am also a believer of...
hard work.
I work hard to get the things I wish for.
I believe that...
someday...
all your wishes will come true.
I hope so.
You might be feeling cold.
Thank you.
So what does William Herrera do?
How are you?
How's life after college?
I just started as a management trainee
in my dad's construction company.
Rich kid.
Rich kid my foot.
I'm not.
- Yes, you are.
- No.
Yes.
But I'm hoping that after six months,
I'll be promoted to project manager.
Assuming that I won't disappoint my father.
Are you not excited?
Do you honestly think
that I dream of working for my dad?
Well, right.
Okay.
If I were to choose,
I would want to be...
a writer.
A writer?
- See?
- For real?
A writer?
Yeah.
Is that so unbelievable?
I am sorry.
That's not what I meant, but...
A writer?
- Yeah.
- I didn't...
I didn't expect
that you'd dream of becoming a writer.
It's not common
to meet someone who wants to be a writer.
Are you saying that it's a worthless dream?
It's not like that.
Okay.
Actually, I'm impressed.
Very impressed, in fact.
How about you?
How is Miss Joycelyn Trinidad?
Surviving.
Okay.
Yes, struggling. But it's manageable.
I do modeling sometimes.
Sometimes a promo girl.
Sometimes an extra on TV or in film.
Actually, I saw you in Lolong.
- You did?
- Yes.
I'm embarrassed, but how was it?
Was I effective in my role?
Well...
Honestly, if there's an award
for the most charming person
getting eaten by a crocodile...
I guess, you will get it.
I don't know
if I should be flattered or annoyed,
but thank you.
You know what?
Life hasn't been easy for me.
But I don't...
I don't have regrets.
I don't want to change anything because...
Humans like us...
We become better every day.
No matter
if we make the right or wrong decisions.
You know what?
I wish I am more like you, Miss Joyce.
Because I have lots of regrets.
Like what?
Like...
I wasn't able to tell the person I liked
how I truly felt.
Why don't you tell her?
You might regret it if you don't.
What if she doesn't like me?
What if she does?
What if...
she's now ready to open her heart to you?
If you were in my place...
what do you think I should do?
Take a leap of faith, Mr. Herrera.
Maybe she's just waiting for you.
Love isn't so mysterious.
People just make it complicated sometimes.
For me, love is very simple.
Love is an act of bravery.
You need to be brave
when you open up your heart to others.
Will you marry me?
- Yes, yes.
- Yes?
- Yes.
- Yes!
Yes!
Thank you!
The baby moved!
He kicked!
There!
Don't you hear it?
- No.
- Why?
Hey, hey.
Why?
Ma'am, we can already see the baby.
Count to three, okay?
Like I said, our story is like no other.
This story is not about
our "happily ever after".
It's about what happens
after "happily ever after".
One, two, three.
Hey, when will you wake up?
It's late! Your son will be late for school.
Must I wake you up every time?
Can't you wake up on your own?
Yes. Yes, hon.
I'm going to get up, so please, relax.
It's too early to get cranky.
Why won't I get cranky?
I have an important meeting.
Look at the time, Liam!
It's already late to leave the house.
It's already rush hour.
We will be stuck in traffic.
Your son is going to be late. So wake up!
Yes, yes. I'm already getting up.
Get up or you will get it from me
if I am late.
I told you we should hit the road by 5:30 AM.
We would be late if we left at 6 AM.
The traffic is already heavy.
Your son will be late again.
I told you I have a meeting
with an important client.
You're compromising even my work.
Hon...
I'm sorry.
I stayed up late revising my presentation.
It's because you procrastinated.
Talk to Dex's class adviser.
She said your son can't afford
to be late anymore.
He has been late many times
in this grading period.
Talk to her and explain.
Tell her it's your fault
that your son is late.
- Hey, what are you doing?
- Hey!
You cut us off!
We're almost at Dex's school.
We can get there faster if we run.
Give me your bag.
- Is this all you need?
- What about me?
Hon, can you book a motorcycle
so you can get to work faster?
Sweetie, be safe, okay?
Mommy's going to work now.
Make sure you eat.
Mommy made you a yummy meal.
It's your favorite.
Make sure to eat it, okay?
I love you.
Love you.
We'll talk later. We can't stay like this.
See you later, Mommy.
Oh no, Daddy.
Mommy is mad at you again.
Sweetie, Mom's not mad.
That's how your mom shows her love.
Straight to the point.
So, are you ready?
Come on.
Let's go.
Let's go?
Who said stories should end
in happily ever after?
Don't worry.
This is not one of those stories.
Who said stories should end
in happily ever after?
Don't worry.
This is not one of those stories.
Like in a movie, this is just a trailer.
Hello, Dex.
Because what happens
after "happily ever after" is more realistic.
It tells a more realistic story of love.
People say
that love is the most powerful force
in the universe.
Others say that love is destiny.
Love is kind.
But for me...
Love is an act of bravery.
Brave enough to open your heart
to less-than-ideal situations.
Brave enough to face the challenges
that time and fate throw at you.
Brave enough to put in the hard work
to make it work.
And this story is about that kind of love.
The truest kind of love.
Hi, son.
Mommy, I have a new tablet.
Daddy gave it to me because I am a good boy.
Where's your daddy?
Over there. Making dinner.
Hon, you're home.
Come on,
let's eat while the food is still hot.
Did I forget something
that we should celebrate?
You did.
And we should really celebrate this, hon.
So it's true that you gave Dex a gift?
Come on.
Don't be jealous.
Do you think it's just Dex?
I also got you something.
Go on. Open it, my love.
[Air Filipinas]
[To: Paris, France]
What is this for?
For us.
Maybe it's about time
we fulfill our dream vacation in Paris.
So there.
Can we talk?
What do you think are you doing?
Where did you get the money for this?
I used my credit card.
So you also bought Dex's tablet on credit?
Hon, just relax.
Let me explain.
Liam, what is there to explain?
You know that we only earn enough.
Barely enough for Dex's schooling.
And now, this?
Are you using your head?
Hon, come on. It's okay.
My new show got approved.
That means we have extra income.
So you think you have money
just because you have a new show?
Like you hit the jackpot?
Are we one-day millionaires?
Liam, we should save when we have extra money
instead of compulsively spending!
What if we have an emergency?
What will happen to Dex?
Where will you get the money?
Hon, I just thought
that maybe we need a break
from stress, you know?
You thought of it?
Did you really think it through?
Liam, are you really using your head?
Huh?
Because if you are,
you should have realized
that we don't need this.
If you only use your head,
you will realize
that we can't afford to go on vacation,
because we will starve after!
Son, love isn't so mysterious.
For me, love is very simple.
Because love is an act of bravery.
You need to be brave
to open your heart to others.
I'm sorry.
Don't worry. I'll return everything tomorrow.
I'll ask for a refund for everything I spent.
Gosh.
Hon.
Hon...
I overslept.
Hon, sorry. I overslept.
My alarm didn't work.
I know. I turned off your alarm.
Looks like you stayed up all night,
so I didn't wake you up.
What?
What about Dex?
Our car was towed, remember?
I called my mom.
I asked her to bring Dex to school for now.
By the way...
Your dad called.
He was cleaning and saw these things
that belonged to your mom.
Why did he bring it only now?
Good thing his new wife didn't get rid of it.
There are photo albums here
that we can show to Dex.
I miss your mom.
I miss her cooking.
We can show these to Dex.
What else is there, hon?
Well... what is this...
What is it?
- Is it heavy?
- What is this?
I wonder what it is.
- I think you open it here.
- This side?
There.
I didn't know
that mom also had something like this.
Was she a writer, too?
I don't know.
I'll put away Mom's things.
Let me do it, hon.
I'll bring it to the storage room.
I got it.
Hon...
I'm sorry for last night.
It's okay.
You were right.
Actually...
I was wrong.
I was wrong because I overreacted.
I know...
that you're just trying
to be a good father...
and a good husband.
I'm sorry because instead of being happy...
instead of thanking you...
I judged you.
I said some hurtful words.
I should be the one to apologize.
I should have been...
I should have been
more mindful in my decisions.
I shouldn't make decisions on my own.
We can still go.
We'll go to Paris?
Don't you want to?
Of course, I do.
But you said we should not spend compulsively
so when there's an emergency,
we have savings.
Hon, you know what?
I am about to close a deal
with a big account later.
If I get that,
I will provide insurance
for all the employees
of a big-time businessman.
Hon, I'm sure
I'll get a huge commission from it.
Wow.
Congratulations, hon.
So that means
our Parisian honeymoon is really on.
Dex will soon have a sibling.
Silly.
Why not?
I love you.
I love you, too. So much.
So much.
After all the stories I told you,
I'm sure you still have some questions left.
What could possibly go wrong?
What?
Are you kidding?
I developed that story for almost a year.
Look, Liam.
I am sorry to be the bearer of bad news.
But the network has decided
not to proceed with your concept.
And that decision has already been made.
Sir, you can't do this to me.
I need this story.
I need this project.
You said you think the story was good,
and it was very promising
when it comes to viewer engagement.
Liam, relax.
Relax?
Sir, how can I relax?
The concept that I've long been working on
is gone!
You have to understand, Liam.
Television is still very traditional.
Your concept is too high.
It's too modern.
Our audience can't relate to it.
So, what now?
- Do I just give it up?
- I didn't say that.
What I'm saying is
there are still other platforms
we can explore.
What do you mean?
What I'm saying is
there is opportunity for it
in the streaming platforms.
Well, generally speaking,
your story is more suitable
for the digital audience.
The highly educated ones
with disposable income.
Young professionals
with unique viewing habits.
So you mean there's still a chance
for my show to get produced?
Of course!
That's why I want to introduce you to Charry.
Your timing is perfect, Liam.
I am really looking for creators like you!
See?
And as they say,
actually, as Gen Z would say,
content is king, and content is our future.
Aren't you excited?
Gosh, there's a lot I want to say,
but I am sure that, you know,
your future is so bright.
Assuming we don't destroy the planet,
your future is really bright.
Content creator, the best. Right?
That's what I've been telling Liam.
- He is one of the network's best writers.
- Wow!
But I think television
is too small a pond for him.
True.
So I honestly believe
we have an opportunity here.
Cha here is the head of DigiTV.
One of the fastest-growing
online content platforms
in the region.
Wow!
Ma'am, it's nice to meet you.
It's an honor for me
to share my passion for storytelling.
Great!
So tell me,
what story do you want to tell?
Oh, why?
Do you have to go somewhere?
N-No, I don't.
I don't have other plans.
It's okay.
No problem.
Okay. So, what are you waiting for?
Pitch your great idea to me, and let's see.
What is it?
Is it a survival game
in a post-apocalyptic world?
- Mom!
- Sweetie.
Bye, Dex.
Let's go.
Dex, why are you still here?
Who will pick you up today?
My daddy.
Maybe he's stuck in traffic.
Okay, just wait here. Okay?
I'll be inside.
Our platinum health insurance
will provide your employees
with comprehensive health benefits.
Aside from hospitalization,
we also provide coverage
if your employee needs long-term therapy,
including mental health services.
She used to be an actress, right?
Her career did not go anywhere
after she got pregnant.
Oh, what a waste.
That's what she got for being a flirt.
She made the wrong choices.
The advantage of this, sir,
is that if your employee gets sick...
[Incoming Call]
Our priority is to provide your employees...
the best healthcare there is.
We will nurse them back to health,
and make them productive again.
But, sir, let me discuss
how much more you can save
by availing our corporate package.
Your mom's not answering her phone.
Let's try calling your dad.
He's also not picking up.
Maybe they're already
on their way here, Teacher.
I'll just wait for them.
I'll go to the office first.
I'll double-check from the file
if I have the correct contact numbers
of your parents.
Stay here, okay?
Sir!
- Sir!
- Boss, to City General.
Sir, where are you going? Sir, wait!
- Let's go.
- Sir!
Don't party too much, sir.
You can be forgetful
when you're having too much fun.
Hey!
Why are you hugging my wife?
He's been acting weird, Ma'am.
I'm worried about his situation right now.
Wait, wait!
Pervert!